<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Entertainment &#8211; W Online Mills</title>
	<atom:link href="https://w.online.mills.edu/category/entertainment/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://w.online.mills.edu</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 13:06:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>South Korea celebrates 10 years of K-pop megastars BTS</title>
		<link>https://w.online.mills.edu/south-korea-celebrates-10-years-of-k-pop-megastars-bts/</link>
					<comments>https://w.online.mills.edu/south-korea-celebrates-10-years-of-k-pop-megastars-bts/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 13:06:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Entertainment]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://w.online.mills.edu/?p=11</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Fans of K-pop megastars BTS flocked to hotspots around Seoul on Monday to mark the supergroup&#8217;s 10-year anniversary, with South Korea unveiling a special commemorative stamp series to celebrate. The group&#8217;s fans &#8212; known collectively as ARMY &#8212; gathered outside the offices of its agency HYBE to take selfies and record TikTok videos in front...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Fans of K-pop megastars BTS flocked to hotspots around Seoul on Monday to mark the supergroup&#8217;s 10-year anniversary, with South Korea unveiling a special commemorative stamp series to celebrate.</p>
<p>The group&#8217;s fans &#8212; known collectively as ARMY &#8212; gathered outside the offices of its agency HYBE to take selfies and record TikTok videos in front of a huge mural of the stars being painted on a wall.</p>
<p>Korea Post unveiled a special edition series of stamps in BTS&#8217;s honour set to go on sale at post offices today, Tuesday &#8212; the official anniversary of the septet&#8217;s debut &#8212; having already sold out almost instantly online.</p>
<p>&#8220;Obviously BTS are global superstars, but we didn&#8217;t expect the stamps to be sold out on the day of the online release,&#8221; a Korea Post official told AFP.</p>
<p>After debuting on 13 June, 2013, the group went on to become the first all-South Korean act to dominate the US and UK charts, raking in billions of dollars and building a global fandom in the process.</p>
<p>&#8220;Many ARMY BTS fans have asked for the release of BTS stamps, and we also wanted to issue stamps for these global artists for their 10th anniversary,&#8221; Kim Mi-hwa, Korea Post stamp designer, told AFP.</p>
<p>The band &#8212; currently on a hiatus, with two members performing their mandatory South Korean military service &#8212; released a new digital single last week to celebrate the anniversary.</p>
<p>The single, ‘Take Two’, is purportedly a nod to the band&#8217;s second chapter after a decade as musicians.<br />
Fans from around the world travelled to South Korea to celebrate the anniversary, with the Seoul city government running a special programme for the visitors.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s thrilling to be here. It&#8217;s thrilling to be surrounded by other ARMY,&#8221; scientist Anne Micic, 55, a BTS fan from Australia, told AFP.</p>
<p>&#8220;I think that&#8217;s the other thing, that as an ARMY when you meet other ARMY it&#8217;s almost like you have another family, which is really awesome.&#8221;</p>
<p>A handwritten letter by J-Hope, who began his military duty in April, was uploaded Monday on Weverse, the worldwide fandom network.</p>
<p>The letter appeared to have been prepared in advance for the anniversary before he joined the military.</p>
<p>&#8220;I assume I&#8217;d be very military-disciplined&#8221; by the time the letter is revealed, he wrote.</p>
<p>&#8220;No matter what day it is, I sincerely thank you and love you,&#8221; he told fans.</p>
<p>&#8216;BTS saved my life&#8217;<br />
A special map released by the city government for fans visiting from abroad features 13 locations across the South Korean capital.</p>
<p>It includes agency HYBE&#8217;s office in Yongsan and the historic Gyeongbok Palace, where BTS filmed a special edition of the Tonight Show with Jimmy Fallon.</p>
<p>Fans said it was worth travelling so far to honour their favourite band.</p>
<p>BTS &#8220;really saved my life&#8221;, Claudia Agustin, 23, a fan from Indonesia who works in accounting, told AFP in Seoul, adding that their lyrics had spoken to her during difficult periods of her life.</p>
<p>She said she was &#8220;really, really proud&#8221; of the group&#8217;s 10-year anniversary.</p>
<p>&#8220;I know how they&#8217;ve been struggling from back in their debut days and then they really make it big. Now everyone really knows them,&#8221; she added.<br />
Starting Monday, important tourist spots across Seoul, including the Namsan Seoul Tower and Dongdaemun Design Plaza, will be lit up in purple &#8212; ARMY&#8217;s colour &#8212; in celebration of the anniversary.</p>
<p>BTS members who are not doing their military service yet have been busy with their solo careers &#8212; with Jimin releasing his six-track solo album ‘Face’ in March.</p>
<p>It is likely part of a carefully planned strategy, experts said.</p>
<p>&#8220;The most significant part of BTS&#8217; 10th anniversary is that they&#8217;re still here and together as BTS,&#8221; Jeff Benjamin, Billboard&#8217;s K-pop columnist, told AFP.</p>
<p>&#8220;Every male K-pop group will need to pause or transition due to South Korea&#8217;s mandatory military service but not every group is adequately prepared as BTS has with preplanned music and content that holds significant meaning.</p>
<p>&#8220;Even the new song itself &#8216;Take Two&#8217; speaks specifically to this new chapter of BTS with their fans,&#8221; Benjamin added.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://w.online.mills.edu/south-korea-celebrates-10-years-of-k-pop-megastars-bts/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
